Hey, did you go anywhere
for summer vacation?
No, nowhere. I worked all summer.
Hey, that sounds nice. You must
have saved a ton of money, huh?
My family went to Hawaii.
Looks a lot like Hateno Island.
Huh? What are you talking about?
The ocean was insanely clear.
I was impressed by how many fish
you could see when you went under.
Hey, Mizuho...
Huh? Who're you?
Sorry, wrong person.
Watch where you're walking.
Sorry.
Seriously...
Did our going adrift ever actually happen?
Took you long enough. I've been waiting.
Oh, the guys in the basketball club
asked me to sub in again.
Those guys sure take me for granted.
Then again,
I know it had to have happened--
being adrift for those two years.
Something's come unfastened. Are we okay?
Right according to plan. It looks
like we just passed the speed of light.
We've arrived at the
entrance to other dimensions.
Huh...
We should start getting ready.
Are you sure you understand what
kind of consequences this will have?
Our original selves are different people.
Still, I don't think
this is the place for us.
You guys are nuts. So was she...
It would have been enough
if you'd never known.
What we've been given is plenty, isn't it?
Neither here nor our original world
will change. You know that, right?
We want to get there on our own.
Nozomi was following her own heart.
The responsibility was her own, after all.
They're all gone now. Even Ms. Aki.
Kossetsu went off to join Hoshi.
Rajdhani's become a forest,
and is living with the animals.
Hateno Island has sunk. It turns out...
...nothing is left here for me.
Go on.
Mm-hmm.
See you.
You must not leave here.
You're not saying that we
can't leave here, then?
We'll be all right this time. Let's go.
Mm-hmm.
How are you going to
take that back with you?
We don't know if Nozomi will be
alive once we get there, do we?
That's why we're using her Compass.
Huh?
None of the outcomes
are going to be changed.
Only the things that can happen
do happen in the world, after all.
So we're going to
re-roll the possibilities.
Tell me, Nagara,
what made you decide to go back?
Because this...
...is the light that Nozomi saw.
Apparently, they're building
apartments here.
Oh, yeah?
I wonder how Grandma's cats are doing.
I heard that Tora passed away.
Oh, really...
Well, he was 13 years old.
He lived plenty long.
The service that took them in is sure
pricey, though. 400,000 yen for just one.
All three cats cost 1.2 million. But for
that price, I'm sure they're doing well.
Everything's gone.
Hey, Mizuho...
Huh? Who're you?
Sorry, wrong person.
Hey, Nagara.
"Rajdhani's parrot laughs."
So you remember.
Mm-hmm.
Is work hard?
Yeah, not too bad.
Maybe I should get a job, too.
Rent an apartment, and take in the cats.
If you don't have to do it,
you're better off not.
There's a lot of other stuff
that you have to do.
I knew that nothing was going to change.
In my mind, I thought I understood that.
This is the future that you chose, right?
Do you remember when you told me
once that we couldn't change the world,
so it would be all right?
Do you still think so now?
Mm-hmm. We really can't change the world.
But this is still the world that I chose.
Standing here, looking back now,
there were just some probabilistic
components at work back there,
and after some time now,
I can't even tell them apart anymore.
Someday, I'll forget this feeling, too,
and do the same thing over again.
I don't know if Nozomi is the
same Nozomi that we knew, either.
But this is the future that she saw.
Have you talked to Nozomi?
No, I've only spotted her so far.
She won't remember going adrift.
Probably not.
I wonder if she's a different person.
I don't know.
You've got work, right?
Well, see you later.
Hey, you'll be fine.
As long as there's still a little of
who you were on that island in there,
you'll be fine.
Mm-hmm.
You were worried about them, too?
I mean, they were chirping at night.
The guy at the station
said that he thought
that maybe their mother
had gotten killed by a crow.
The others were all dead,
but this little one is still alive.
Will you look after it?
Huh? No, I'm not allowed to have pets.
We went to the same
middle school, didn't we?
Mm-hmm. You transferred in during
the second term of 3rd year, right?
Nozomi...
Ah, sure enough,
their mother never came back.
This is the only one still alive.
Oh? So what are you going to do with it?
Hmm, I think I'll look
after it until it can fly away.
Our lives are only beginning. What lies
ahead will take just a little bit longer.